<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ServerManagerConfiguration>
    <ProxyGroup name="filters">
        <!-- ==================================================================== -->
		<SourceProxy class="vtkThreshold"
                 name="Threshold">
      <Documentation long_help="This filter extracts cells that have point or cell scalars in the specified range."
                     short_help="Extract cells that satisfy a threshold criterion.">
                     The Threshold filter extracts the portions of the input
                     dataset whose scalars lie within the specified range. This
                     filter operates on either point-centered or cell-centered
                     data. This filter operates on any type of dataset and
                     produces unstructured grid output. To select between these
                     two options, select either Point Data or Cell Data from
                     the Attribute Mode menu. Once the Attribute Mode has been
                     selected, choose the scalar array from which to threshold
                     the data from the Scalars menu. The Lower Threshold and
                     Upper Threshold sliders determine the range of the scalars
                     to retain in the output. The All Scalars check box only
                     takes effect when the Attribute Mode is set to Point Data.
                     If the All Scalars option is checked, then a cell will
                     only be passed to the output if the scalar values of all
                     of its points lie within the range indicated by the Lower
                     Threshold and Upper Threshold sliders. If unchecked, then
                     a cell will be added to the output if the specified scalar
                     value for any of its points is within the chosen
                     range.</Documentation>
      <InputProperty command="SetInputConnection"
                     name="Input">
        <ProxyGroupDomain name="groups">
          <Group name="sources" />
          <Group name="filters" />
        </ProxyGroupDomain>
        <DataTypeDomain name="input_type">
          <DataType value="vtkDataSet" />
          <DataType value="vtkHyperTreeGrid" />
        </DataTypeDomain>
        <InputArrayDomain name="input_array"
                          number_of_components="1">
        </InputArrayDomain>
        <Documentation>This property specifies the input to the Threshold
        filter.</Documentation>
      </InputProperty>
      <StringVectorProperty command="SetInputArrayToProcess"
                            element_types="0 0 0 0 2"
                            label="Scalars"
                            name="SelectInputScalars"
                            number_of_elements="5">
        <ArrayListDomain attribute_type="Scalars"
                         name="array_list">
          <RequiredProperties>
            <Property function="Input"
                      name="Input" />
          </RequiredProperties>
        </ArrayListDomain>
        <Documentation>The value of this property contains the name of the
        scalar array from which to perform thresholding.</Documentation>
      </StringVectorProperty>
      <DoubleVectorProperty command="ThresholdBetween"
                            default_values="0 0"
                            label="Threshold Range"
                            name="ThresholdBetween"
                            number_of_elements="2"
                            panel_widget="double_range">
        <ArrayRangeDomain name="range">
          <RequiredProperties>
            <Property function="Input"
                      name="Input" />
            <Property function="ArraySelection"
                      name="SelectInputScalars" />
          </RequiredProperties>
        </ArrayRangeDomain>
        <Documentation>The values of this property specify the upper and lower
        bounds of the thresholding operation.</Documentation>
      </DoubleVectorProperty>
      <IntVectorProperty command="SetAllScalars"
                         default_values="1"
                         name="AllScalars"
                         number_of_elements="1">
        <Hints>
          <PropertyWidgetDecorator type="InputDataTypeDecorator"
                                         name="vtkHyperTreeGrid"
                                         exclude="1"
                                         mode="enabled_state" />
        </Hints>
        <BooleanDomain name="bool" />
        <Documentation>If the value of this property is 1, then a cell is only
        included in the output if the value of the selected array for all its
        points is within the threshold. This is only relevant when thresholding
        by a point-centered array.</Documentation>
      </IntVectorProperty>
      <IntVectorProperty command="SetUseContinuousCellRange"
                         default_values="0"
                         name="UseContinuousCellRange"
                         number_of_elements="1">
        <Hints>
          <PropertyWidgetDecorator type="InputDataTypeDecorator"
                                   name="vtkHyperTreeGrid"
                                   exclude="1"
                                   mode="enabled_state" />
        </Hints>
        <BooleanDomain name="bool" />
        <Documentation>
          If off, the vertex scalars are treated as a discrete set. If on, they
          are treated as a continuous interval over the minimum and maximum. One
          important "on" use case: When setting lower and upper threshold
          equal to some value and turning AllScalars off, the results are
          cells containing the isosurface for that value.  WARNING: Whether on
          or off, for higher order input, the filter will not give accurate
          results.
        </Documentation>
      </IntVectorProperty>
      <IntVectorProperty command="SetInvert"
                         default_values="0"
                         name="Invert"
                         number_of_elements="1">
        <Hints>
          <PropertyWidgetDecorator type="InputDataTypeDecorator"
                                   name="vtkHyperTreeGrid"
                                   exclude="1"
                                   mode="enabled_state"/>
        </Hints>
        <BooleanDomain name="bool" />
        <Documentation>Invert the threshold results. That is, cells that would have been in the
          output with this option off are excluded, while cells that would have been excluded from
          the output are included.
        </Documentation>
      </IntVectorProperty>
      <Hints>
        <Visibility replace_input="2" />
      </Hints>
      <!-- End Threshold -->
    </SourceProxy>
    </ProxyGroup>
</ServerManagerConfiguration>